(Penny:)Interesting.
(Penny:)I never told you that.
(Leonard:)Sure you did.
No.
(Penny:)I never told anyone that.
(Penny:)But I did write it
in my journal.
(high-pitched):
What?
I didn't know you had a journal.
(Penny:)I also know your voice
gets higher when you're lying.
(deeply):
No, it doesn't.
(Raj:)You know, this reminds me
of high school.
(Emily:)You worked in
a restaurant?
(Raj:)No, I was in India...
it was humid and smelled funny.
(Howard:)All right, I think
I'm getting into a groove here.
(Howard:)This isn't so bad.
(Emly:)Only five hours
and 40 minutes to go.
(Howard:)We've only been
doing this 20 minutes?!
(Raj:)You know, I read that
(Raj:)washing dishes can be an
excellent form of meditation.
(Raj:)The key is that while
washing the dishes